{"game_code":"7MXIHFQI","level_name":"qwqw","questions":[{"answer":"Data","incorrect":["Information","Files","Knowledge"],"question":"This is the basic building block of information, and it becomes meaningful when processed or interpreted."},{"answer":"It is raw and unprocessed","incorrect":["It is easily understood","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"What is the primary characteristic of data?"},{"answer":"Information is derived from processing and organizing data","incorrect":["Information is always in a raw and unprocessed state","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"Which of the following statements is true about information?"},{"answer":"Data communications","incorrect":["Data encryption","Computer programming","Graphical user interface"],"question":"The exchange of information in binary form between two connected devices, whether directly or through a network?"},{"answer":"Interfacing","incorrect":["Synchronization","Signal Generation","Recovery"],"question":"It is one of the communication tasks which refers to the need to convert the input data (digital) into a suitable form (analog) for transmission and vice-versa during reception."},{"answer":"Recovery","incorrect":["Signal Generation","Addressing and routing","Transmission system utilization"],"question":"It allows the system to resume an activity previously interrupted by an unexpected fault in the system. What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Exchange management","incorrect":["Synchronization","Addressing and routing","Interfacing"],"question":"It is the agreement between devices on various conventions, such as transmission method (simplex, half or full duplex), data block length, data format, error detection and correction, and how fast data must be sent. What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Synchronization","incorrect":["Signal Generation","Transmission system utilization","Interfacing"],"question":"It is one of the communication tasks wherein it allows the receiver to determine when a signal begins, and when it ends, and how long each signal element is."},{"answer":"System management","incorrect":["Protection","Signal Generation","Exchange management"],"question":"It is one of the communication tasks wherein it is required for configuring and monitoring the system, allowing it to react rationally to failures and overloads, and to effectively plan for future expansion."},{"answer":"Addressing and routing","incorrect":["Transmission system utilization","System management","Protection"],"question":"It ensures that in multi-user environment, the information is sent to the correct destination, and that the best possible route to this destination is chosen. What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Transmission system utilization ","incorrect":["Interfacing","System management","Synchronization"],"question":"It is the need to efficiently use various transmission facilities that are commonly shared by other devices? What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"A segment cable fault affects all workstations","incorrect":["Bus Topology is easy to implement.","It is easy to extend","Low cost"],"question":"Which of the following is the disadvantage of Bus topology?"},{"answer":"Equal access for all users","incorrect":["Expensive Adaptor Cards","Difficult Connections","Malfunctioning workstations and cables create problems for the entire network"],"question":"Which of the following is an advantage of Ring topology?"},{"answer":"Centralized network/hub monitoring","incorrect":["Hub can be a single point of failure","Hubs are slightly more expensive than thin-Ethernet","Requires more cable than most other topologies"],"question":"All of these are disadvantages of Star topology except?"},{"answer":"255.255.255.0","incorrect":["255.255.0.0","255.0.0.0","255.255.255.255"],"question":"What is the default subnet mask for Class C IP address?"},{"answer":"Class C","incorrect":["Class A","Class B","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the address 192.168.10.1 belong?"},{"answer":"Class B","incorrect":["Class A","Class C","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the address 172.0.1.2 belong?"},{"answer":"Class C","incorrect":["Class A","Class B","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the address 200.10.18.15 belong?"},{"answer":"Class A","incorrect":["Class C","Class B","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the address 10.11.23.14 belong?"},{"answer":"Class B","incorrect":["Class C","Class A","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the address 185.24.12.23 belong?"},{"answer":"192.168.2.5","incorrect":["200.168.0.2","128.170.2.5","192.168.0.255"],"question":"Which of the following is the dotted-decimal notation for the binary IP address: 11000000 10101000 00000010 00000101 ?"},{"answer":"129.11.11.239","incorrect":["192.168.0.1","110.101.110.111","255.0.0.1"],"question":"What is the dotted-decimal notation for the binary IP address: 10000001 00001011 00001011 11101111 ?"},{"answer":"249.155.251.15","incorrect":["128.64.32.16","255.255.255.255","249.155.250.1"],"question":"What is the dotted-decimal notation for the binary IP address: 11111001 10011011 11111011 00001111 ?"},{"answer":"11000000 10101000 00001010 00000101","incorrect":["10101010 10101010 10101010 10101010","11110000 00001111 11110000 00001111","11000100 11101000 01001010 00001011"],"question":"What is the binary representation of the IP address: 192.168.10.5 ?"},{"answer":"00001010 00010100 00011110 00101000","incorrect":["10101011 11001100 00101000 00101000","00001010 11110100 00011110 00101000","00111010 00010100 00011110 00101000"],"question":"Determine the binary representation of the IP address: 10.20.30.40 ?"}],"time":82}